# REED **SANDERS**

332 W Knollcrest Dr Peoria, Il 61614 · 309-634-5379

rpsanders@mail.bradley.edu · linkedin.com/in/reed-sanders-44a2071ba/

Detail-oriented individual offering skills in supporting users with technical knowledge and troubleshooting abilities. Stays on top of demands in fast-paced environments by effectively using slow periods. Strong passion for cybersecurity. Highly motivated to learn from new experiences and put in the work to make the company and self better.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### SEPTEMBER 2021 – PRESENT

### IT INTERN, OSF HEALTHCARE

- Provide level 1 support to employees and patients from several hospitals, corporate offices, and doctor's offices relating to requests for IT services.
- Promptly resolve or triage requests by providing the most effective and efficient solution.
- Check and give security access to databases and applications using active directory.
- Ensure proper documentation and use of knowledge database.
- Worked closely with clients and end-users to define needs and break down problems.
- Solving IT issues over the phone, text chat, and remote access.
- Worked effectively with a diverse team to accomplish daily objectives and meet long-term goals.
- Resolved issues with medical documentation software, Microsoft Office, and an assortment of other programs used in the medical field.
- Prepared incident reports, including compiling, entering, and organizing data.

#### SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

# SALES ADVISOR/GEEK SQUAD AGENT, BEST BUY

- Assist customers to select the computer/electronic that best fits their needs.
- Setup up new computers and update older ones.
- Remove viruses.
- Install applications on clients' computers.
- Troubleshoot a wide variety of issues with computers, phones, and printers.
- Performed troubleshooting and diagnosis for issues related to software and peripheral equipment.
- Maintained detailed records of daily support activities and resolutions.
- Diagnose broken Apple devices and document damage for proper repair.

#### **DECEMBER 2016 – SEPTEMBER 2019**

# **CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST, HYVEE**

- Accountability Helped ensure customers were getting the best shopping experience possible.
- Resolving customer issues.

- Overseeing the checkout process.
- Processed refunds, exchanges, and store credits for customers facing issues.
- Maximized satisfaction by anticipating needs and consistently offering expert support.
- Manage Excel spreadsheets and inventory management software.

# **EDUCATION**

**MAY 2023** 

# BACHALORS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BRADLEY UNIVERSITY

- CONTENTRATE IN WEB, SOFTWARE, AND COMPUTER SECURITY
- MINOR IN CYBERSECURITY

**MAY 2019** 

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, PEORIA NOTRE DAME

# **SKILLS**

- Java
- C++
- Microsoft Office
- Kali Linux
- Python
- C

- Data security
- Ticket management
- Troubleshooting and diagnosis
- Computer workstation setup
- Networking